Mister!
[Episode 10]
Hey, Minchae.
What? Yun collapsed?
Why? What's wrong?
Okay.
Okay. I'll be right there.
Yeah. I'm leaving now.
Mister.
Minchae! Can you call her cell again?
Said she'll come, so she'll be here soon.
It's been 30 minutes already. Where did she say she is?
Where is she coming from?
I didn't ask her.
Why is that brat doing this to me?
Yun!
Yeah?
Why are you doing this?
Huh?
I'm saying this because I care.
Stop confusing her.
She gets confused even if you tell her directly.
I'm not going to make her feel confused anymore.
I won't. Don't worry.
Do I look sick, Minchae?
I'm dating Eunchae.
Yun collapsed?
Why? What's wrong?
Okay.
Yeah, Minchae. I'm in front of the house.
Yeah. I'm coming inside soon. Is Yun okay?
Eunchae.
Hey, Minchae.
Eunchae. What did you do to Yun?
I think Yun's in shock because of you.
I heard his heart is damaged from the car accident.
Why don't you be more careful?
I'll tell Mom some excuse.
That's the best for all of us.
Uncle?
Uncle, why are you sleeping here?
It's cold here. Wake up.
Mom! Let's go get some sweet cakes.
Galchi! Uncle is sleeping on the ground.
It's blood...
Uncle! Uncle! Uncle!
What do I do?
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Uncle! Uncle!
Wake up!
Here. Help me.
Uncle...
[Recent Calls:
Song Eunchae, Song Eunchae, Song Eunchae]
[Song Eunchae]
Don't answer it...
Yun.
Don't move. Stay with me.
You were awake?
Yeah. I was awake from the start.
I made Minchae lie to make you come here.
I think I'm crazy, Eunchae.
I can't stand being without you.
Maybe I really do need to grow up like you said.
I think I've become a baby.
Like a baby that cries when his mother is away.
I won't ask you to stay forever.
Just until I fall asleep.
Stay until I fall asleep. Please?
I think I'm crazy, Eunchae.
I can't stand being alone without you.
So pretty! Such a pretty car!
Is it really Eunchae's car?
I know. It's our car now.
I'm so happy!
I can't stop smiling!
When the Bosamos hear about this
they'll die from jealousy!
All those that looked down on me
would have nothing to say!
What's "Bosamo"?
Botox lovers community.
I can't hold it in much longer.
Choi Yun is going to be my son-in-law!
At least twelve people will go crazy from jealousy!
I know! Myeongsuk, Mija, Yeongsuk...
When I tell them Yun is going to be my brother-in-law,
They'll want to move out of the country.
I didn't know you were so good at counting...
Counting all those chickens before they hatch...
What are you talking about? Aren't you going to school?
Go to school!
Okay! I'll go! You're so materialistic!
I wonder if this really is the best for all of us.
Is Eunchae happy?
What are you babbling about?
This is a secret.
But doesn't it feel like Yun hurt
his head in the accident rather than his heart?
I know. I was thinking the exact same thing!
Jinx.
Right? I mean, how could a guy like Yun like Eunchae
unless he had brain damage?
I know!
She's my daughter but realistically and objectively,
it's too good to be true.
I know!
So he doesn't even look at Kang Minju anymore?
Yeah.
But... What if he comes to his senses?
What? Comes to his senses?
If his brain recovers...
He'll take the car back, I'm sure.
If he breaks up with Eunchae...
What will happen to Eunchae?
We would be so doomed.
I know...
Let's have the wedding before he comes to his senses!
Let's just do it!
How about that?
Mom!
Hey, don't you think we are being
too awful and selfish?
I know.
What? What did you say you want to do?
Get married.
I want to marry Eunchae. Water!
What? Are you feeling okay?
Eunchae's changed. I'm worried.
She's different.
If I don't do something, she might run away.
What's wrong?
Mom, I think I need Eunchae.
No, I must have her, Mom.
I don't understand. Do you have a fever?
I'm alive because of Eunchae.
When I had the accident...
I can't explain it, but Eunchae saved me.
I need to have Eunchae.
No matter what, I need to have Eunchae.
Help me.
Help me, Mom. Okay?
You're really not sick anymore?
Yeah, I'm okay now.
I was so shocked, I thought I
was going to have a heart attack.
Don't get sick again.
Okay.
Are you jealous of the boys with their dads?
No. I have you, my uncle.
That's right! You've got a cool,
handsome uncle right here!
We'll come here every day from now on...
And every day we'll...
Raise your arm...
Uncle...
Huh?
Don't go to Australia.
What?
Stay and live happily ever after with us.
I'll be good and study really hard.
And I'll tell Mom not upset you.
You won't go, right?
Don't go, okay? Don't leave, Uncle.
Okay, you little brat!
Lee Galchi! Raise your arm!
You're so dirty!
[Missed call: Mister Pervert]
I'm going out.
- Where are you going?
- What?
Yun isn't working today. Where are you going?
Oh...
Meeting Muhyeok?
Want to have a drink with me instead?
- Right now?
- Yeah, now.
It's still daytime, Dad.
Is there a rule against day drinking?
Give me a minute. Let me get dressed.
Bottoms up!
Okay.
Dad.
Yeah?
I'm a bit drunk now...
We're only on our fourth bottle.
Since when were you so soft, my daughter?
What's on your mind, Dad?
About Muhyeok...
Forget him before it gets serious.
Dad...
Even if it's already serious...
Don't do it. Forget him.
Why? Because of Yun?
I don't want Yun anymore, Dad.
Coming and going whenever he calls...
I'm not a dog.
Let's move. I'll look for a new house.
Also quit being his coordinator.
Do you want to go back to school?
How about studying abroad?
Dad. I'm sorry.
But I can't forget Muhyeok.
Eunchae...
I was lonely and sad when I liked Yun...
But not with Muhyeok.
I feel grateful and warm.
I worry so much that Muhyeok might be
sad and lonely because of me.
Eunchae...
I can't forget him now...
I can't forget him, Dad...
Huh? Where'd the bullet go?
Isn't it amazing that I'm still alive... Sir?
Have a seat.
You must have been in a lot of pain lately.
It's my first time seeing my brain like this.
Unbelievable...
The bullet is embedded between the blood vessels,
adding more and more pressure
to your brain as time passes.
The blood vessel is getting weaker
and thinner as it stretches.
I didn't come here to hear all that.
Prescribe me some medicine.
Cha...
Muhyeok!
Mr. Cha Muhyeok.
I can withstand the pain.
But I get nosebleeds, get dizzy
and pass out everywhere.
That's all I need you for. It's making life tough.
It must be very tough these days.
Until I die, let me live a great life,
not a pathetic one
where I'm vomiting, bleeding,
and passing out everywhere.
Give me something.
Medicine... Give me some medicine!
It must be so tough.
It's not tough!
I told you. I'm not here for your sympathy!
I'm here because I'm embarrassed to live like this!
I'm just asking for the sake of asking...
But... Are you not capable of saving my life?
It's just, you look a lot smarter
than my fat, Australian doctor.
I guess not.
The increasingly painful headaches, the nosebleeds...
Do those mean I haven't got much time left?
And lastly...
One more question.
Is death really my only option?
Ma'am!
The doctors here are quacks! Don't go in.
Don't go!
What a sight!
The whole family is nuts...
Yes?
Blockhead!
Be careful.
When my dad wakes up,
will you tell him I had to go?
Thank you.
Are you gonna be okay?
I'll be fine. Goodbye.
Oh, no. What should I do?
Eunchae.
Mister.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Cold, huh?
Come here.
Are you warm?
Let's be fair.
What?
I'm super drunk, so you have to be drunk, too.
It's only fair.
Fair is my favorite word in the whole world.
Why did you drink so much during the day?
I had my reasons.
You know.
One of those days you can't handle reality sober.
I'm having one of those days, too.
See? We're so perfect for each other, aren't we?
Here!
Chaser.
You get kinder and kinder.
And you listen to me... Such a good boy.
Open this one.
You don't have much of a tolerance, do you?
He's passed out after half a bottle of soju.
I wanted to confess something to you
after getting you drunk.
I had something tell you...
Mom...
You're sleeping here?
Don't you have a home?
Mommy!
Mister!
Mommy...
I have a husband! I'm married! With children!
Just sleep! Unless you want to die.
We're even now, aren't we?
Eunchae's changed. I'm worried.
She's different.
If I don't do something, she might run away.
Just a moment, Mr. Choi Yun.
Yes?
Here's the new album.
- Wow, it's already done?
- It's really good.
Thank you.
- See you later.
- Okay.
How have you been?
Bad.
Why?
I'm just reaping what I've sowed,
being punished for hurting you.
There's no need. Is love an obligation?
Don't feel guilty.
We should think this was meant to happen.
You'll still be my friend, right?
You've become pretty cool, Choi Yun.
Sad that you've lost me, huh?
Little bit.
Mrs. Song said, "You have to be
burned to come to your senses."
I've been burnt. And I've come to my senses, finally.
How is it going with Eunchae?
How about you and that guy?
You should get going, huh?
I'll give you a ride. You can't drive yet, right?
Are you sure you should be working right now?
I heard your heart isn't so healthy.
I'm fine. Doctors always try to scare you.
Rockhead.
Eunchae?
I wish I could walk all night
with you on my back like this.
Wanna come with me?
If you came with me... I'd be so happy.
I'd be really happy if you'd just come with me.
This would be the best way to die.
With you on my back.
We're here.
Let's do another lap around the neighborhood.
Eunchae...
Give her to me.
Give her to me. I'll take her.
Give Eunchae to me!
Eunchae. Song Eunchae!
Wake up. Wake up, Song Eunchae!
Let me down, Mister.
Let me down.
Yun.
Let's go home.
Let me go.
What are you doing? What are you doing, Yun?
- Let go. Let my hand go!
- Let her go!
She said to let go!
Don't disrespect her.
Blockhead...
Sweet dreams.
Are you dating Muhyeok?
No.
It's okay then.
Go. Sweet dreams
I...
I want to take Muhyeok's hand.
You don't need me.
You've always been fine without me.
You'll be fine without me.
But Muhyeok...
Eunchae!
Let me go.
Please, Yun?
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
In the middle of the night?
Why? Is there something wrong?
Yun! Yun?
Yun!
What's wrong?
Eunchae!
No. You're wrong. This couldn't be.
Run the tests again. I said test him again.
Test him again. It doesn't make sense.
It just doesn't make sense, doctor.
That's why I asked that he avoid stress.
But... He was fine. He was fine.
Didn't you see him on TV? He was healthy and fine.
Actually, we didn't expect it
to get worse so suddenly, either.
Yun's symptoms aren't external.
So you have to be careful at all times.
I can't accept it. I won't. Run the tests again.
I don't believe for a second that
a boy that healthy is terminally ill.
Does that make sense, doctor?
I'm going to get a second opinion.
I'll take him to a different hospital right now!
Calm down. Please.
Please. Save him.
Please save him.
My Yun is the only blood descendant I have.
He is my life.
I'll give you everything I have. Anything.
Please. Just... Just save him. Please, doctor.
We'll do our best.
His best option is a transplant.
But it won't be easy.
Transplant? Do you mean a heart transplant?
Take my heart!
Please. Save him. Take my heart to save him.
I'll do anything. To save him, I can do anything.
I've lived long enough. It's fine.
I can't live without my Yun. I can't.
I'll die as well if my Yun dies, doctor.
Mrs. Oh!
Ma'am!
I can do anything if it's to save my Yun.
I'll even give you my heart.
Please, save him with my heart, doctor.
Your hand saved me.
During the accident...
I was thinking, "So this is how I die.
I guess this is the end."
Then suddenly, I heard your voice.
It's okay, Yun. It's going to be okay.
It's nothing.
Don't go anywhere. Don't listen to anything.
Just hold my hand tight.
It's okay, Yun. It's nothing.
My Yun is the only blood descendant I have.
He is my life.
Over here.
So you lived in Australia?
Yes.
What kind of people were the parents that raised you?
I don't remember.
I don't want to remember.
Was it a hard life?
No, because I knew I'd be back here some day
to find my birth mother who was
too poor to raise her child
and wanted to buy her a house and
take her out to fancy restaurants.
Because I had hope, it wasn't hard at all.
So... Did you find your mother?
No.
Did you sleep well?
Yeah.
Seed.
This is a pirate.
A monster.
- What's this?
- A fingernail.
It's a skull.
Next.
Skull again.
Circle. Spacecraft.
Do you know anyone in Korea?
Even if you like me that much...
All the way from Australia? Why did you come here?
You Korean?
You're Korean?
I'm saved! Saved!
Love is just a game to me.
Where'd you go?
If you had come any later...
Hey!
Hey, mophead!
You don't even know anyone here,
and yet you still came for me?
In any case, thank you...
For liking a girl like me.
Dear Lord,
if you really do exist, I promise you this.
About Song Eunchae.
If you'll let me have her for my remaining days...
I could stop everything right now.
And go in peace.
Transplant? Do you mean a heart transplant?
Take my heart! Please. Take my heart to save him.
No way... A ghost story for a weak-hearted person?
It's okay. Just tell me.
They don't scare me anymore.
I can't think of any right now.
Have you heard the one with the elevator ghost?
I don't know.
A kid was on his way home after class...
What's wrong, Yun?
Are you okay?
Sorry, let's go inside.
Okay. Breathe in...
Good. Now...
Mr. Choi Yun?
Blockhead!
Hang out with me, Blockhead!
Hang out with me for one minute.
I have to go to Yun.
Mister.
I'll save him.
I'll save Yun.
Mister.
So don't cry.
I can't stand watching you cry.
You look as ugly as Shrek when you cry.
I'll give my heart to Yun, okay?
Mister.
I'll give my heart to Yun,
so will you be with me?
Will you just stay with me while I'm still alive?
[Episode 11 Preview]
Did you think about it? What's there to think about?
It's good for you, me, Yun, and Yun's mom.
Bastard...
You know how to cuss, Blockhead?
Fine, take it out! Give your heart to him!
Take it out!
How can you stoop that low?
Death is not a joke.
[Sorry, I want to have you even if it's like this]
[Love, even if it costs me my life]